A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 2, Series 10 FA1448
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 2, Series 10
1998-2015
2000-2010
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1448
47.68 Cubic Feet 123 letter-size document boxes, 2 legal-size document box.
Arrangement
Records remain in original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an RAC archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. These specific grant files were transferred to RAC in multiple accessions in 2013-2015.
Scope and Contents
Each grant file often contains records pertaining to: budget and administration, proposals and development, articles and background information, correspondence, grant products and related program files. The grants represented in this series primarily span 2000-2010.
- University of Pittsburgh - Degenholtz (20070774), 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- University of Pennsylvania - Naylor (20040068), 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
- University of Pennsylvania - Naylor (20040068), 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
- University of Pennsylvania - Naylor - Phase 2 (20050336), 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- University of Pennsylvania - Naylor - Phase 2 (20050336), 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20070770) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20070770) - Grant Products, 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20070074), 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20070770), 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20070074) - Grant Products (Box 4, Folder 2)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20070074) - Correspondence, Proposal Development, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20060105), 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20060105) - Grant Products, 2005-2009 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20060105) - Proposal Development, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20060105) - Articles and Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20050067), 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20050067) - Grant Products (Box 5, Folder 5)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20050067) - Proposal Development, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Rogal (20050067) - Correspondence, Articles and Background, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- AcademyHealth - Helms (20040412), 2004-2009 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Helms (20040412) - Grant Products, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Helms (20040412) - Correspondence, Proposal Development, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- AcademyHealth - Helms (20040412) - 2004 Colloquium, 2004 June 5 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Chicagoland Chamber of Commerce - Wasson (20030273), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- George Washington University - Biles (20070780), 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- George Washington University - Biles (20070780) - Grant Products, 2007-2010 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
- George Washington University - Biles (20060162), 2005-2008 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
- George Washington University - Biles (20060162) - Grant Products, 2007-2009 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- George Washington University - Biles, Rosenbaum (20070651) (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Center for Health Strategies - Bella (20100020), 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Bailit Health Purchasing (20110246), 2010-2011 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- University of Massachusetts Medical School - Ash (201000003), 2009-2012 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Center for Health Strategies - Bella (20080221), 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- Johns Hopkins University - Anderson (20060716), 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Mathematica Policy Research - Verdier (20060362) - Dirigo Evaluation Proposal (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Urban Institute - Holahan (20060740) - MA Healthcare Reform Evaluation, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Health Management Assoc. - Silow-Carroll - Proposal, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Center for Health Care Strategies - Somers - Proposal, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Center for Health Care Strategies - Bella (20060673), 2002-2006 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Weil (20050559) - Proposal, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Weil (20050559), 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- University of Kansas - Langer (20040706), 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
- AcademyHealth - Martinez-Vidal (20060636) (Box 12, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Guterman (20050633), 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Kanye (20040339), 2006 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- DMA Health Strategies - Dougherty (20060055) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Rutgers University - Cantor (20060405) (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Economic Social Research Institute (ESRI) - Silow-Carroll (20050203), 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- The National Academies of Science - Hurtado (20010197), 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Harris Interactive, Inc. - Taylor (95-09) - Working Group Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Primary Care Development Corporation - Chin, Kotelchuck (20010002), 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20060547), 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Wilson-JFK School of Government - Congressional Retreat (20010434), 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center (20000719) (Box 13, Folder 9)
- President Fellowship of Harvard College - Wilson (20000759) (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Kehoe (20020653), 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Kehoe (20020653) - Grant Products, 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20010153), 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20010153) - Preliminary Data, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- MC Quality Survey Analysis (20010153) - Disparities in Quality of Health Care (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Quality of Care (20010153) - Survey Report Meeting, 2002 January 9 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Quality of Care Survey (20010153) - Women's Gender Analysis, 2002 April 16 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Spragens and Associates, Inc. - Spragens (20031439) (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Spragens and Associates, Inc. - Spragens (20031439), 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Sheps Center - Sloane - Bathing Without A Battle (PDF 20030149), 2002-2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Long Term Care Community Coalition (LTCCC) - Rudder (20050012), 2003-2009 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Long Term Care Community Coalition (LTCCC) - Rudder (20050012) - Correspondence, Articles, 2004-2009 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Long Term Care Community Coalition (LTCCC) - Rudder (20050012) - Proposal Development, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Long Term Care Community Coalition (LTCCC) - Rudder (20050012) - Grant Products (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Long Term Care Community Coalition (LTCCC) - Rudder (20050012) - Grant Products (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Brown University - Mor (20050318) (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Brown University - Mor (20050318) - Proposal Development, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Brown University - Mor (20050318) - Correspondence, Articles, 2004-2007 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Brown University - Mor (20050318) - Grant Products (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Massachusetts Long Term Care Foundation - Bonner (20080338) (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Cornell University - Meador (20080436) (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
- Cornell University - Pillemer (20070273) (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Cornell University - Pillemer (20070273) - Products and Meetings, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Cornell University - Pillemer (20070273) - Proposals, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Farrell (20040697) (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
- Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Farrell (20040697) - Budget and Administration (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Farrell (20040697) - Proposal Development (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Farrell (20040697) - Correspondence and Articles (Box 20, Folder 3)
- The Health TV Channel - Bedrosian (20010501) (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Harris Interactive, Inc. - Taylor (20020348) (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Harris Interactive, Inc. - Taylor - Strategic Health Perspectives (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Harvard University - JFK School of Government - Wilson (20020523) (Box 21, Folder 2)
- National Initiatives for Children's Health Care Quality (20030120), 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Long Term Care Community Coalition - Mollot (20100006), 2009-2011 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Carlson (20040839) (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Carlson (20070510) (Box 22, Folder 4)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Carlson (20070510) - Proposal Development (Box 22, Folder 5)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Carlson (20070510) - Grant Products (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Carlson (20100332) (Box 23, Folder 4)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Carlson (20100332) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Pioneer Network in Culture Change - Kantor (20100496) (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
- Pioneer Network in Culture Change - Kantor (20100496) - Grant Products (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
- Pioneer Network in Culture Change - Kantor (20090566), 2009-2010 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Pioneer Network in Culture Change - Kantor (20090566), 2009-2010 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Pioneer Network in Culture Change - Kantor (20090566) - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
- University of Maryland - McDiarmid (20070075), 2006-2007 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- University of Maryland - McDiarmid (20070075), 2006-2008 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- University of Maryland - McDiarmid (20070075) - Grant Products, 2007-2010 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- New York University (NYU) - Mezey (20080332), 2008-2009 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
- New York University (NYU) - Mezey (20080332), 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Tufts Medical Center, Inc. - Neumann (20090203), 2008-2010 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- President and Directors Georgetown College - Hoadley (20110455), 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Center for Health Care Strategies, Inc. - Bella (20090034), 2008-2010 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- The Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20090093), 2008-2011 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - McHugh (20080278), 2008-2010 (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
- University of Alabama (Birmingham) - Wray (20070646) (Box 28, Folder 4)
- University of Alabama (Birmingham) - Wray-Ashton (20070646) - Grant Products, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- University of Alabama (Birmingham) - Wray-Ashton (20070646) - Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
- AcademyHealth - Arnold (20070743) (Box 29, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Arnold (20070743) - Grant Products, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Arnold (20070743) - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- The Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20070781), 2007-2009 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- The Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20070781) - Proposal Development, 2007-2008 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- The Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20070781) - Grant Products, 2008-2009 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Kaiser Foundation Research Institute - Hsu (20070551), 2007-2009 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
- Quality Partners of Rhode Island - Besdine (20050411), 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Quality Partners of Rhode Island - Besdine (20050411) (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
- LeadingAge, Inc. - Benner (201006554), 2010-2012 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- LeadingAge, Inc. - Benner (201006554) - Grant Products, 2009-2012 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Massachusetts Senior Care Foundation - Bonner (20090386), 2008-2010 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
- LeadingAge - Minnix (20100076), 2008-2011 (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
- LeadingAge - Minnix (20100076) - Grant Products (Box 32, Folder 5)
- LeadingAge - Minnix (20100076) - Grant Products (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
- AARP - Reinhard (20090552) (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
- AARP - Reinhard (20090552) (Box 34, Folder 1)
- AARP - Reinhard (20100068), 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 2-3)
- AARP - Reinhard (20100068) - Grant Products, 2009-2011 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- New York University (NYU) - Mezey (20090293), 2009-2011 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- New York University (NYU) - Mezey (20050691), 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- New York University (NYU) - Mezey (20050691) (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
- George Washington University - Markus (2011002), 2010-2011 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- National Association of Health Data Organizations - Love (20090601), 2009-2010 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Singer (20080261) (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Center for Health Care Strategies - Highsmith (20100470) (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Center for Health Care Strategies - Highsmith (20100066), 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- The Joint Commission - Schyve (20080055), 2007-2010 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- DMA Health Strategies - Holt (20090462) (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Johns Hopkins University - Guyer (20020707), 2002-2005 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
- National Institute for Children's Health Care Quality - Fubel (20090288), 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Association of Maternal and Child Health Programs - Fraser (20090245), 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Connecticut Children's Medical Center - Antonelli (20070632), 2007-2009 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Health Management Associates - Silow-Carroll (20100279) (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Child Health and Development Institute of Connecticut - Honigfeld (20080112), 2007-2009 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Center for Health Policy Developmet - Kaye (20070767), 2005-2010 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Center for Health Policy Developmet - Kaye (20080149), 2007-2009 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
- Center for Health Policy Developmet - Kaye (20060611), 2005-2009 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
- Center for Health Policy Developmet - Kaye (20060611) - Grant Products (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
- George Washington University (20090088) (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
- UCLA - Halfon (20070064), 2006-2009 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- UCLA - Halfon (20070064) - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- UCLA - Halfon (20070064) - Proposal, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- UCLA - Halfon (20070064) - Grant Products, 2007-2008 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Rutgers University - Reinhard (20020439) (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Kaye (20090343), 2009-2010 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Kaye (20090343) - Proposal, 2003-2010 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Kayne (20090343) - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Kayne (20090343) - Correspondence, 2008-2010 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- George Washington University - Ferguson (20070735), 2007-2009 (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
- American Institutes for Research (AIR) - Moon (20050382) (Box 41, Folder 4)
- American Institutes for Research (AIR) - Moon (20050382) - Grant Products (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - Maulik (20110516) (Box 41, Folder 6)
- George Washington University - Rosenbaum (20060212), 2005-2006 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Rutgers University - Reinhard (20020439) (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Rutgers University - Reinhard (20020439) (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
- Rutgers University - Reinhard (20020439) (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Minnesota Department of Human Services - Olson - State Solutions (20020535) (Box 43, Folder 2-4)
- National Academy of Sciences - Olsen (20080299), 2008-2010 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
- Mathematica Policy Research - Livermore (20070501) (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Mathematica Policy Research - Livermore (20070501) - Proposals, Articles and Background (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Mathematica Policy Research - Livermore (20070501) - Grant Products, 2007-2009 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences - Larson (20090375) (Box 45, Folder 1)
- University of Texas (Austin) - Lambrew (20080010) (Box 45, Folder 2)
- The Brookings Institution - McKethan (20090556) - Medicare Accountability, 2009-2010 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Jewish Healthcare Foundation of Pittsburgh - Miller (20100090), 2008-2010 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Tufts New England Medical Center - Neumann (20060590), 2006-2008 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Tufts New England Medical Center - Neumann (20060590) - Proposal, Correspondence, 2006-2008 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Tufts New England Medical Center - Neumann (20060590) - Grant Products, 2007-2008 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Council of Accountable Physician Practices - Taylor (20090543) (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Research Triangle Institute - Trisolini (20070120), 2006-2007 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Research Triangle Institute - Trisolini (20070120) - Grant Products, 2006-2007 (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
- Research Triangle Institute - Trisolini (20070120), 2006 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20100281), 2009-2010 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20100383) (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20100383) - Proposal Development (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20100383) - Grant Products (Box 47, Folder 4)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20050634), 2005-2008 (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20050634) - Grant Products, 2005-2008 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20050634) - Grant Products, 2005-2008 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- American Health Quality Foundation - Deutsch (20060256), 2006-2008 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- American Health Quality Foundation - Deutsch (20060256) - Grant Products, 2006-2009 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Robinow Consulting - Robinow (20090553) - Global Payment Models (Box 48, Folder 4)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20080016) - Medicare, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20040184) (Box 49, Folder 1)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20040184) - Proposal Development and Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20040184), 2004-2006 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- National Association of Health Data Organizations - Love (20100310), 2009-2011 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Center for Health Care Strategies - Somers (20040676), 2000-2006 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Center for Health Care Strategies - Somers (20040676) - Grant Products, 2004-2006 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Center for Health Care Strategies - Somers (20040676) - Proposal Development (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Chassin (20030088) (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Chassin (20030088) - Grant Products, 2002-2004 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Chassin (20030088) - Proposal Development (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Harvard Medical School - Guadagnoli (20030185) (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Harvard Medical School - Guadagnoli (20030185), 2003-2005 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Harvard Medical School - Guadagnoli (20030185) - Proposal Development, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Harvard Medical School - Guadagnoli (20030185) - Grant Products, 2003-2005 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance - Scholle (20060277) (Box 51, Folder 4)
- New England Health Care Institute - Everett (20060153), 2005-2008 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- George Washington University - Siegel (20040622), 2004-2007 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Latino Health Institute - Laws (20050244), 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Chassin (20060124), 2005-2008 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Patti (20080320), 2008-2011 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Patti (20080320), 2008-2009 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20060125), 2006-2011 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- University of Alabama, Birmingham - Weech-Maldonado (20060692), 2006-2007 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- University of Alabama, Birmingham - Weech-Maldonado (20060692) - Proposal Development (Box 53, Folder 4)
- George Washington University - Ku (20100307), 2009-2012 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Metter (20070539) (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Center for Studying Health System Change - Reschovsky (20060591), 2004-2007 (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
- Society for Development and Behavioral Pediatrics - Trimm (20080431) (Box 54, Folder 5)
- National Public Health and Hospital Institute - Regenstein (20020728) (Box 54, Folder 6)
- National Public Health and Hospital Institute - Regenstein (20020728) - Proposal Development (Box 55, Folder 1)
- National Public Health and Hospital Institute - Regenstein (20020728) - Grant Products (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Northwestern University - Hasnain-Wynia (20070222), 2007-2010 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Other Commonwealth Fund Sponsored Proposals, 2004-2006 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- National Association of Community Health Centers - Hawkins (20060512), 2005-2006 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- George Washington University - Regenstein (20080130) (Box 56, Folder 1)
- International Society for Quality in Health Care - Tregloan (20050108), 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences - Mitchell (20060048), 2006-2008 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- The Commonwealth Fund - Beal, 2005-2006 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Drexel University -Andrulis (20080287) (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Brandeis University - Altman (20110248), 2010-2011 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Margolis (20020711), 2002-2008 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Margolis (20020711) - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Margolis (20020711) - Proposal Development and Grant Products (20020711), 2002-2007 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Nuzum (20070533) (Box 57, Folder 2)
- University of Massachusetts - Schoen (20050607) (Box 57, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Adams (20060484) (Box 57, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Adams (20060484) - Breakfast, 2006 February 7 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- AcademyHealth - Adams (20060484) - Scorecard (Box 57, Folder 6)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Reede (20090560) (Box 58, Folder 1)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Reede (20090560) - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 58, Folder 2-3)
- March of Dimes - Fleischman (20090578), 2009-2010 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
- Greater New York Hospital Association - Johnson (20100549) - Grant Products (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Greater New York Hospital Association - Johnson (20090546) - Proposal, Grant Products (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Summit Health Institute for Research and Education - Perot (20000478), 2000-2001 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20010153) - Survey Tables and Analysis (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
- Brandeis University - Gittell (20020185), 2000 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20070066) (Box 60, Folder 2)
- International Society for Quality in Health Care - Tregloan (20070396) (Box 60, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Martinez-Vidal (20060636) (Box 60, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Guterman (20070532) - Medicare's Future, 2007-2008 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- AcademyHealth - Nuzum (20060624), 2006-2007 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Health Management Associates - Silow-Carroll (20070046) - States in Action Newsletter, 2006-2007 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Blumenthal (20060615) (Box 60, Folder 8)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Reede (20080381), 2008-2010 (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Reede (20080381), 2008-2011 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
- Center for Studying Health System Change - Reschovsky (20090500), 2009-2010 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Trustees of Dartmouth College - Fisher (20060456), 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 4)